=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 10=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 10 =
Why did you prepare dinner for me?
لماذا أعددت العشاء لي؟
I know you
أنا أعرفك
like these dishes.
مثل هذه الأطباق.
I will cook for you every day.
سوف أطبخ لك كل يوم.
OK?
نعم؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I wanna marry you.
اريد ان اتزوجك
Eh?
ايه؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You said you wanna marry me in the morning.
قلت أنك تريد الزواج مني في الصباح.
Why do you regret it now?
لماذا تندم الآن؟
Mo Chen,
مو تشين ،
I heard what you said in the study that day.
سمعت ما قلته في الدراسة في ذلك اليوم.
I know why you pretend to be lame.
أنا أعلم لماذا تتظاهر بأنك أعرج.
I know why you broke up with me.
أنا أعرف لماذا انفصلت عني.
I know everything.
انا أعرف كل شيء.
You know everything?
أنت تعرف كل شيء؟
Yes.
نعم.
But it's OK,
ولكن كل شيء على مايرام،
I don't mind.
أنا لا أمانع.
You don't mind?
لا تمانع؟
Yes.
نعم.
Love knows no gender.
الحب لا يعرف الجنس.
You must have had a hard time.
لابد أنك مررت بوقت عصيب.
What are you thinking about
بم تفكر
every day?
كل يوم؟
Ah?
آه؟
You
أنت
are not
غير صحيح
gay?
مثلي الجنس؟
So you and Xu Weilai...
إذن أنت و Xu Weilai ...
Go.
يذهب.
(Party A: Mu Qingyun Party B: Mo Chen)
(الطرف أ: حزب مو تشينغيون ب: مو تشن)
So,
لذا،
you want to marry me
انت تريد الزواج مني
because of this shareholding agreement?
بسبب اتفاقية المساهمة هذه؟
Mr. Mu wants me to help you.
السيد مو يريد مني مساعدتك.
So,
لذا،
he gave me the appropriate shares.
أعطاني الأسهم المناسبة.
I never thought
لم أظن طلاقا
marriage was a deal.
كان الزواج صفقة.
Ah!
آه!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I don't want to keep it from you anymore
لا أريد أن أمنعه عنك بعد الآن
or do anything
أو افعل أي شيء
that makes you misunderstand due to this agreement.
الذي يجعلك تسيء الفهم بسبب هذه الاتفاقية.
I've figured it out.
لقد اكتشفت ذلك.
My father must have cooperated with you
لابد أن والدي تعاون معك
to defend the Mu Group.
للدفاع عن مجموعة Mu.
What do you think, Mr. Mo?
ما رأيك يا سيد مو؟
Do you dare
هل تجرؤ
to cooperate with the new director
للتعاون مع المدير الجديد
of the Mu Group?
من مجموعة مو؟
(Hello, everyone.)
(أهلا بالجميع.)
(There are a lot of rumors)
(هناك الكثير من الشائعات)
(about me on the Internet recently,)
(عني على الإنترنت مؤخرًا ،)
(My fiancee and I)
(خطيبتي وأنا)
would like to clarify it.
يود توضيح ذلك.
(The Mu Group's Press Conference) (The video of the hotel was taken)
(المؤتمر الصحفي لمجموعة مو) (تم التقاط فيديو الفندق)
(by our competitor to maliciously spread rumors.)
(من قبل منافسنا لنشر الشائعات بشكل ضار).
(My fiancee doesn't have a night out)
(خطيبتي لا تقضي ليلة في الخارج)
(with a new boyfriend.)
(مع صديقها الجديد.)
Mu Liu did this.
فعل مو ليو هذا.
What should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Tomorrow is the deadline
غدا هو الموعد النهائي
for her to get out of the Mu Group.
لها للخروج من مجموعة Mu.
Fortunately, Mo Chen finally stood up,
لحسن الحظ ، نهض موشن أخيرًا ،
which is the power of love
وهي قوة الحب
and
و
a miracle of life!
معجزة الحياة!
(You are just a fake couple.)
(أنتما مجرد زوجين مزيفين).
(They were just for fun. The rich say one thing and do another.)
(كانوا من أجل المتعة فقط. الأغنياء يقولون شيئًا ويفعلون شيئًا آخر.)
(Are you cheating kids? )
(هل تغش الأطفال؟)
(The Engagement Press Conference The Live Room of the Mu Group's News.)
(المؤتمر الصحفي الاشتباك الغرفة الحية لأخبار مجموعة Mu.)
(The Mu Group's people are like this? You see the man is reluctant.)
(شعب مجموعة مو مثل هذا؟ ترى الرجل متردد.)
(Is this the rich people's marriage? Is Mr. Mo under duress?)
(هل هذا زواج الأغنياء؟ هل السيد مو تحت الإكراه؟)
(You two seem too unconvincing. Please take more convincing actions.)
(يبدو أن كلاكما غير مقنعين للغاية. يرجى اتخاذ إجراءات أكثر إقناعًا.)
(The explanation is unconvincing. Don't explain since you have been shot.)
(التفسير غير مقنع. لا تشرح له منذ أن تم إطلاق النار عليك).
We've explained everything.
لقد شرحنا كل شيء.
Why don't they believe it?
لماذا لا يصدقون ذلك؟
(Why do you want to marry me?)
(لماذا تريد الزواج مني؟)
(I can't let my aunt take the Mu Group.)
(لا يمكنني السماح لعمتي بأخذ مجموعة Mu.)
(I'll help you.)
(سوف اساعدك.)
Why don't they trust me?
لماذا لا يثقون بي؟
(Mo Chen is so proactive! What is it?)
(مو تشن استباقي للغاية! ما هو؟)
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
(OK! So sweet!)
(حسنًا! حلو جدًا!)
(I think there's nothing wrong with it) ♪From the Milky Way♪
(أعتقد أنه لا يوجد شيء خاطئ في ذلك) ♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪
(So sweet!)
(حلوة جدا!)
(Wow! That's good! Congratulations!)
(واو! هذا جيد! تهانينا!)
(Show affection in public! Bless you!) ♪The resin lights the torch♪
(أظهر المودة في الأماكن العامة! باركك!) الراتنج يضيء الشعلة
♪To brighten the starry sky at night♪
لتفتيح السماء المرصعة بالنجوم ليلاً ♪
You...
أنت...
What did you do?
ما الذي فعلته؟
You just kissed me,
لقد قبلتني للتو
making it almost get out of hand.
مما يجعلها تخرج عن نطاق السيطرة تقريبًا.
The explanation is useless.
التفسير غير مجدي.
I just helped you.
لقد ساعدتك للتو.
Can you
هل تستطيع
help me to the end?
ساعدني حتى النهاية؟
Just say what you want.
فقط قل ما تريد.
Tomorrow is the shareholders' meeting.
غدا هو اجتماع المساهمين.
I'm afraid I can't handle it.
أخشى أنني لا أستطيع التعامل معها.
Can you teach me some tips?
هل يمكنك أن تعلمني بعض النصائح؟
Ouch!
أوتش!
Don't you watch the way when you walk?
ألا تشاهد الطريق عندما تمشي؟
If I hadn't been in a meeting today,
إذا لم أكن في اجتماع اليوم ،
I had to teach you how to behave.
كان علي أن أعلمك كيف تتصرف.
Oh?
أوه؟
Everyone came early.
جاء الجميع مبكرا.
I'm already sleepy from waiting.
أنا بالفعل نعسان من الانتظار.
I thought Ms. Mu was afraid to come.
اعتقدت أن السيدة مو كانت تخشى المجيء.
Looks like you're all ready,
يبدو أنك جاهز تمامًا ،
then I'll start.
ثم سأبدأ.
Do you think a live broadcast
هل تعتقد أن البث المباشر
can change
يمكن أن تتغير
your bad behavior in recent years?
سلوكك السيئ في السنوات الأخيرة؟
You were ostensibly marrying Mo Chen
لقد كنت تتزوج ظاهريًا من مو تشن
but secretly allied with Mr. Song,
لكن متحالفين سرًا مع السيد سونغ ،
damaging our company's reputation.
الإضرار بسمعة شركتنا.
You also used Mr. Song to embezzle public funds.
لقد استخدمت السيد سونغ أيضًا في اختلاس الأموال العامة.
Eh?
ايه؟
It's none of my business.
إنه ليس من شأنى.
It was Mu Liu who made me do that.
كان مو ليو هو من جعلني أفعل ذلك.
Luckily, he knew he was wrong
لحسن الحظ ، كان يعلم أنه كان مخطئًا
and gave me your criminal evidence.
وأعطاني دليلك الجنائي.
Please look at the screen.
يرجى النظر إلى الشاشة.
Stop!
قف!
Stop that!
اوقف هذا!
Who are you trying to frame me?
من الذي تحاول تأطير لي؟
Ms. Mu,
السّيدة.  في،
your performance is really wonderful.
أداؤك رائع حقًا.
Since your performance is over,
منذ أن انتهى أدائك ،
it's my turn.
انه دوري.
Please look at the files in your hands.
يرجى إلقاء نظرة على الملفات بين يديك.
You use my signature
أنت تستخدم توقيعي
to transfer the group's funds
لتحويل أموال المجموعة
to a private account through Song Yuan.
لحساب خاص من خلال Song Yuan.
You also want to cheat me
أنت أيضا تريد خداعي
and let me transfer the rest of
واسمحوا لي أن أنقل بقية
the Mu Group's shares to you.
أسهم Mu Group لك.
And your shares in the Mu Group
وأسهمك في مجموعة Mu
have been almost sold by you.
تم بيعه تقريبًا بواسطتك.
You are really anxious to betray the Mu Group.
أنت حقًا متشوق لخيانة مجموعة Mu.
Security,
حماية،
take her out
خذه الى الخارج
to the relevant authorities.
إلى السلطات المختصة.
I'll go by myself.
سأذهب بنفسي.
Then our succession meeting
ثم اجتماع الخلافة لدينا
for new directors can continue.
للمديرين الجدد يمكن أن تستمر.
I disagree!
أنا أعترض!
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪